

6/33-35 Railway St, Kogarah, NSW, 2217 DOB: 08/08/2001

kerryqian@hotmail.com 0478540545

FULL-STACK | AI | DIGITAL MODELLING | AUTOMATION

QUALIFICATION SUMMARY

Bachelor of Computational Design (Distinction) graduate from the University of New South Wales with over two years of experience in the AEC industry. Aiming to leverage a proven knowledge of full-stack development, AI, and Digital Modelling skills to succeed within your company.

KEY SKILLS

- ✓ Easily grasp new concepts
- ✓ Rhinoceros3D / Grasshopper
- ✓ Azure Storage

- ✓ Fluent in English
- ✓ Adobe Software ✓ Digital fabrication
- ✓ Python, C#, JS, React ✓ Strong social skills

- ✓ Limited proficiency in
- Chinese/Mandarin

RELEVANT PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Consultant, Computational Design

Jun 2023 - Present

Aurecon

- Developed Grasshopper library to:
 - o Automate Retaining Wall modeling for various projects
 - Automate exporting of section drawings
- Automating the uploading and filing of team document library.
- Using Convolutional Neural Networks to automate core logging process for the Geotech
- In charge of development of digital initiatives within the Ground and Underground Engineering team.
- Full stack development (JS, React, Azure Storage)
 - Team equipment booking website
 - o Creating capability specific chatbots
 - Webpage storing workflows for global company

Intern Jun - Aug 2021 Greening Australia Sydney

- Created a prototype tool for the "GER-X" Project.
- Using Rhino3D/Grasshopper, I developed a tool to simulate the growth of trees and vegetation on any topography over any time period.
- Able to run sunlight analysis to see shading and sunlight radiation effects on land.

ADDITIONAL EXPERIENCE

TechnicianAsian Traveller

Jun 2016 - Present
Hurstville, NSW

Independently fix computer-related issues around the office including internet, computer, and printer issues.

- Understanding and resolving client issues.
- Organising and maintaining office network and wiring.
- On-call servicing
- Web design

Assistant Mar 2014 – May 2016
Best I.T Solutions Allawah, NSW

At a young age, I developed a strong understanding on computer hardware and software. I can confidently fix/identify the problem of most computer issues.

- Developed a strong interest in problem solving skills through working independently on troubleshooting tasks.
- Developed a deep understanding of computer hardware and software components.
- Doing door-to-door services alone and identifying and fixing problems.

Senior Staff Member

Oct 2019 – Feb 2021

Zambrero

Waterloo, NSW

Working my way from a junior to senior staff member at Zambrero, I developed a strong understanding of how businesses work and how to handle more responsibilities.

- Developed skills to become a strong independent worker.
- Developed skills to work within small teams.
- Able to work within stressful/fast-paced environments.
- Developed leadership skills needed as a Senior staff member.

Attendant Jun 2021 – Jun 2023

Bankstown Sports Club

Bankstown, NSW

Graduated: May 2024

During my time working here, I have been trained in multiple different positions within the club and have been highly adaptable and able to pick up new skills very quickly.

- Ability to co-operate within a large and diverse team.
- Work and communicate with multiple different members of staff.
- Train new staff (preferred trainer).
- Strong customer service skills.

EDUCATION

UNSW Kensington, NSW

- 2021 Dean's List Award.
- 2022 Dean's List Award.
- Data project selected to be featured in the Walden Pond Magazine.
- Fabrication of 'Glass Station' nominated for UNSW 2021 Luminocity exhibition.
- Generative urban planning tool featured in UNSW 2022 Luminocity exhibition.
- Distinction High Distinction on most courses

High School Certificate

Alexandria Park Community School (selective)

- Mentor and assistant for Y12 Music class
- Music Excellence Award.
- Band 6 Music.

Graduated: Sep 2019 Alexandria, NSW